We've been fighting every day, every night, because we currently have half a million lives in the balance.
Half a million Haitians who have been calling these United States of ours home.
Some of them, two years, four years, many of us, 20 plus.
Coming tomorrow, if we do not get a redesignation, an extension of TPS for Haitians,
we are going to start one of the major family separations in modern history.
We are going to see over 100,000 U.S.-born children being ripped from their families.
We are going to witness those children when their parents are kidnapped, taken, and deported without any support.
What we are asking, and demanding, and urging, and praying for is to keep those families together.
What we are asking, and praying, and asking of those Haitian brothers and sisters who have become our neighbor.
So as we continue to push, we have currently asking the President to please reconsider.
And we are urging him tomorrow to redesignate an extension of TPS for Haiti.
We have been called for such a time as this to protect those who have nowhere else to go.
They cannot go back to Haiti.
So it is our duty to fight for freedom.
It is our duty to continue to push.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.